Land Date of Birth: Jun 18, 1989

Email: akrami.ui@gmail.com
Land https://linkedin.com/in/iakrami
Phone: +98 912 0258 031

BACK-END:

FRONT-END:

DATABASE:

OTHER SKILLS:

Linux (CentOS, Debian)

Web Application Security

Bash Scripting

Docker

Git

LANGUAGES:

Persian English (B2) German (A2)

ALIREZA AKRAMI

Summary

Creative Web Developer with 4+ years of experience on web applications' security, and 2 years of experience on Linux system administration and managing databases. I am able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting. I have developed many organizational web applications with PHP and NodeJS and Currently I am looking for a job as a back-end developer.

Experience

BRTech

IT Operations Team Leader May 2019 – Present Tehran, Tehran, Iran



- ${\boldsymbol {\checkmark}}$ Plan, organize, direct, control and evaluate the operations on system
- ✓ Ensuring maximum uptime for all applications on system
- \checkmark Planning any upgrades and expansions for system
- ✓ Leading technical support team and monitoring team

BRTech

Technical Support Engineer
September 2018 – May 2019 (Promoted to IT Operations Team Leader)
Tehran, Tehran, Iran



- ✓ Maintaining and Upgrading over 15+ Linux CentOS servers on Operation Environment
- ✓ Maintaining PostgreSQL databases and MongoDB Cluster

Ansar Bank

Web Security Specialist
March 2014 – September 2018 (4 years 7 months)
Tehran, Tehran, Iran



- ✓ Analyze, monitor, track, and report behaviors and tasks logged by assets (web applications, systems, networks) in the form of incidents to ensure network and systems are protected from any potential leaks of information or malicious activities.
- ✓ Installation, maintenance and monitoring of web security tools to protect systems and data
- ✓ Performing vulnerability scanning for network devices, web applications and databases to identify vulnerabilities. (WebInspect, Nessus ...)
- ✓ Analyze and assess security incidents and escalate incidents by following incident plan
- ✓ Analyze security information and event management (SIEM) tools and services to identify and respond to events as appropriate. (Arcsight)
- ✓ Working with IT teams to solve information security system problems and issuing in a timely and accurate manner
- ✓ Configuring and updating web firewall (FortiWeb)
- ✓ Developing web security tools and scripts (PHP, python)

Education

K.N.Toosi University of Technology

M.Sc. Information Technology, e-Commerce 2012 – 2014

Tehran, Tehran, Iran



Thesis: User Behavior Analysis on Social Networks based on Fuzzy Cognitive Maps

University of Isfahan

B.Sc. Information Technology

2007 - 2012

Isfahan, Isfahan, Irar

Thesis: Analyzing Internet Users' Behavior based on Their Traffic Usage

